



ulasdurmus1@gmail.com



+905533449147



İstanbul, Türkey



linkedin.com/in/ulas-durmus

COMPUTER SKILLS



Unity

Bootstrap

Html5

Wordpress

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Turkish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

German

Elementary Proficiency

Ulaș Durmuş

Electric & Electronic Engineer

I combined my theoretical knowledge that gained through my Electrical and Electronic Engineering education with my computer skills by doing research to improve myself. As a curious, open to learning and enthusiastic person, I think that will add value to your company while working and at the same time contribute to my skills and knowledge.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Electric & Electronic Engineering

Mersin University / Engineering Faculty

09/2017 - 09/2022 Mersin / Türkiye

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Designer

Freelance

06/2020 - Present İstanbul

I designed official websites for companies such as Kalıp Teknik, İpek Rulman, Dere Teknik and much more. Achievements/Tasks

- Building a website from zero based on wordpress
- Entering all products which companies producting
- Fixing bugs and consulting with owners regularly

Engineering InternBiocoder Technology

06/2022 - 07/2022

Achievements/Tasks

Making electronic circuit board drawings with Kicad program

- Making resorces abot sensors and reporting developments to higher unit
- Supporting the company's IOT projects

Engineering InternBekiroglu Engineering

08/2022 - 09/2022

Achievements/Tasks

Drawing electrical wiring with Autocad

Mersin / Turkey

Mersin / Turkey

INTERESTS

Camping

Cycling

American Football

PERSONAL PROJECTS

The Ghost Hunter (01/2021 - 04/2021)

- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.UlasDurmus.TheGhostHunter&hl=tr&gl=US
- My first project to improve myself in mobile game programming.

Captain Edgar Giza (06/2021 - Present)

- https://store.steampowered.com/app/1682040/Captain_Edgar_Giza/
- □ I have been supporting the project in the development phase of the steam game, which has been

Producting and design of incubator device (09/2021 - 06/2022)

 $lue{}$ We coded as a team, the software of our device, which we use pid control systems, to the adruino